Huy Nguyen

in linkedin.com/in/huy-nguyen-454a6016a

github.com/HuyNguyenAu

huynguyen.space

About Me

I'm a curious individual and an avid learner with professional full stack software engineering experience. I thrive on tackling interesting and difficult challenges.

Skills

Languages: C# Typescript Javascript
Libraries: .NET 6.0 React NextJS
Tools: .Docker Azure DevOps
Platforms: .Windows Linux MacOS

Education

Computer and Network Engineering (Honours)
Mar 2016 to Mar 2020

Work Experience

Software Engineer

JET Charge | Oct 2021 - Present

- Development of on-premise and autonomous EV charging load management system and web interface.
- Development of cloud platform EV smartcharging management and optimisation system.

Graduate IT Specialist

EnergyLocals | Sep 2019 - Sep 2020

- Developed and deployed full stack white labeled customer sign-up website.
- Deploy and maintain cloud servers required for business and IT day-to-day activities.
- Research and assist in purchasing, installing, testing, and configuring IT equipment.

IT Specialist

EnergyLocals | Sep 2020 - Oct 2021

- Deployed the Standard Data Interchange Environment for multiple participants.
- Deployed WebMethods Integration Server for FRC Hub.
- Documented IT issues and solutions.

Projects

Loop

An attempt to replicate Microsoft Loop front end.

GPT Decoder

A simple GPT decoder for educational purposes following Andrej Karpathy's 'Let's build GPT: from scratch, in code, spelled out' with some optimisations.

Wobbly ML

A machine learning library using the the Neural Networks From Scratch book.

Lox Crystal Lang

A Crystal programming language implementation of the Lox programming language using the Crafting Interpreters book.